<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>UfoCourier Blog</title>
        <link>https://ufocourier.com/blog</link>
        <description>UfoCourier Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Our Mentor - Mali M. Baum]]></title>
            <link>https://ufocourier.com/blog/mali-m-baum</link>
            <guid>mali-m-baum</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Our Mentor - Mali M. Baum]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" alt="Our Mentor - Mali M. Baum" src="/assets/images/Mali_M_Baum_w-88f0cf79e691428103bd4ffbdcb14253.jpg" width="1200" height="800" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>We are glad to meet our mentor - <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/mali-m-baum-0353b027/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Mali M. Baum</a>.</p><p>Mali is a serial entrepreneur, investor, mentor and community leader, Podcaster Mali Talkshow.</p><p>She is a key person in shaping Female Founders Future and opportunities at the Startups Ecosystem in Berlin/Germany and Europe founded one of the biggest and the most significant network and community, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/w-lounge-berlin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">WLOUNGE</a> for startups, VCs, and corporates supporting Female founders and diverse teams. Mali is an active expert and Jury at the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/european-commission/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">European Commission</a> EIC, and connecting the tech ecosystem together for economic growth and success stories.</p><p>It's a pleasure for us to have a mentor like Mali. We are confident that under her leadership, our UfoCourier startup will quickly gain momentum and with her advice and guidance we will be able to bring our idea to life.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>UfoCourier</category>
            <category>Mali</category>
            <category>Mentor</category>
            <category>Leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome Nataliia]]></title>
            <link>https://ufocourier.com/blog/nataliia</link>
            <guid>nataliia</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Nataliia, Oksana and Pawel from UfoCourier at the SIBB Deep Tech Accelerator]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" alt="Nataliia, Oksana and Pawel from UfoCourier at the SIBB Deep Tech Accelerator" src="/assets/images/SIBB_Nataliia_Oksana_Pawel-b2d3ff80866e95bccc0a3b87205108c4.jpg" width="1081" height="741" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>Congratulations and welcome to UfoCourier, <a href="/team#nataliia-medvedenko-coo-co-founder">Nataliia</a></p><p>Our company is growing and changing every day and we're thrilled to have you
along for the ride. We’re all going to grow together here, and we look forward to
it!</p><p>We hope you’ll speak up, push us to new heights and share your thoughts.
That’s what helps us grow!</p><p>UfoCourier - let's grow together!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>UfoCourier</category>
            <category>SIBB</category>
            <category>Nataliia</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Great news with SIBB]]></title>
            <link>https://ufocourier.com/blog/sibb</link>
            <guid>sibb</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Oksana and Pawel from UfoCourier at the SIBB Deep Tech Accelerator]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" alt="Oksana and Pawel from UfoCourier at the SIBB Deep Tech Accelerator" src="/assets/images/SIBB_Oksana_Pawel-c109a7324615869936b99d0bdbd7a335.jpg" width="1200" height="1224" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>We are really excited to be accepted to <a href="https://www.sibb.de/scholarship" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SIBB Deep Tech Accelerator</a> 2022/23!</p><p>The <em>SIBB Deep Tech Startup Accelerator</em> supports early stage tech projects in product development, market entry &amp; startup formation and we are happy to become a part of this amazing network, meet incredible mentors and take our UfoCourier to the next level.</p><p>Over the next 8 months, we will be working together on startup development support to prepare for launching our business idea and grow.</p><p>Stay tuned to track what's happening with UfoCourier! Let’s the journey begin!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>UfoCourier</category>
            <category>SIBB</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UfoCourier at Startupnight]]></title>
            <link>https://ufocourier.com/blog/sturtupnight</link>
            <guid>sturtupnight</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pawel from UfoCourier and Erfan from Spotliked at Startupnight]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" alt="Pawel from UfoCourier and Erfan from Spotliked at Startupnight" src="/assets/images/startupnight-c03e47bdcf3fade40c4d23a60957de0c.jpeg" width="1600" height="900" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>Today I was a guest at <a href="https://www.startupnight.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Startupnight</a> in Berlin, accompanied by <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/husnakorani/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Husna Korani</a> and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/erfan-nazmehr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Erfan Nazmehr</a> (here in the picture on the right), the founders of <a href="https://spotliked.de/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Spotliked</a>.</p><p>Husna and Erfan, a great and strong team, shared with me some insights into the workings of their startup. As part of the <a href="https://www.sibb.de/scholarship" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SIBB Deep Tech Accelerator</a>, they introduced it to me.</p><p>The Startupnight turned out to be a great event for me to meet investors, but especially emerging startups.</p><p>I'm already looking forward to next year, when UfoCourier will be in the spotlight 🚀</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>UfoCourier</category>
            <category>Startupnight</category>
            <category>SIBB</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UfoCourier Kick-Off]]></title>
            <link>https://ufocourier.com/blog/kick-off</link>
            <guid>kick-off</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[UfoCourier]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" alt="UfoCourier" src="/assets/images/ufocourier_transport-0f53721ffba724b9c3a167dc3e7ecb25.jpg" width="1444" height="800" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>Today is a special day. Today our work on our idea UfoCourier was "officially" started.</p><p>UfoCourier is a platform for sending packages or giving rides by independent drivers, even to the most remote places. With our platform anyone can be a courier.</p><p>The idea for the platform came from personal need. Thousands and millions of Ukrainians living abroad want to send packages to family back home. However, with the use of established logistics service providers, this is a costly and lengthy process. A number of individual drivers have recognized this and are already offering rides, organized through social networks.</p><p>We would like to offer the above groups a platform from which everyone involved can benefit without restricting them.</p><p>Oksana, experienced in business and with special insights into the logistics industry will be our CEO and Pawel, experienced software developer and consultant will be our CTO.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>UfoCourier</category>
            <category>Kick-Off</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>